<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Superhero Genes - Activatable Super Genes</name>
  <author>alite</author>
  <packageId>SuperheroGenes.Activatables</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>ludeon.rimworld.biotech</packageId>
      <displayName>Biotech</displayName>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>SuperheroGenesBase.Mod</packageId>
      <displayName>Superhero Genes - Base</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2980061828</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>

  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
    <li>SuperheroGenesBase.Mod</li>
  </loadAfter>

  <description>
This mod makes super genes slightly more balanced by making the Super Genes have an activatable ability associated with them instead of constant stat bonuses. For example, instead of always having a massive bonus to strength, the pawn gains an activatable ability that grants the same stat stat boosts (Carry Capacity * 100 and Melee Damage * 20), in exchange for the pawn consuming 1.75 times as much nutrition while the ability is active. They will maintain their super states for half an hour, after which they will require another half an hour to recover that power.

WARNING: The food loss multipliers do multiply with each other, so activating 3 at once will result in your super consuming nutrition at over 5 times the normal rate.

This will make superheroes weaker overall, as they can no longer use their full abilities constantly, because if they do you may find your food supply draining very quickly. This was made as a separate mod because some people may not want their superheroes to be more balanced for base game. For a full list of what is taken from the base super gene, look at the images above.

This is CE Compatible


[url=https://discord.gg/fYP8qkcNDh]Discord link[/url] for those who want an easier way to ask questions, make requests, or just chat. I'll also be posting new releases there.

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/alite/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Easy link to all of my Rimworld mods[/url]

[url=https://github.com/KonradHeinser/ActivatableSuperGenes][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url]
[url=https://ko-fi.com/alite56114][img]https://i.imgur.com/Utx6OIH.png[/img][/url]
  </description>
</ModMetaData>

